-[buzzing]
-[barking]
-[whimpering]
-[door rattling]
[electronic buzz]
[dramatic music playing]
What are those codes? The codes,
the codes, the Battle…
the Battle of f… [spluttering]
fish, f… fa-da-fet. Fish fillet.
17 oh, 17 something.
17, something, something.
[alarm blares]
-Oh!
-[noises from room]
-…5.
-[alarm blares]
-No!
-[Cupcake barks]
[clattering]
-…56.
-[alarm blares]
No!
[Cupcake barks]
-[loud thud]
-[ineffective banging on door]
-Aha!
-[battle music swells]
[whimpering]
[clattering]
[bang]
-[tearing]
-[foreboding music plays]
[soft grunt]
-[thud]
-[Cupcake barks, bee buzzes]
Oh… no! Um…
Voice override. She had a voice override.
[beep]
1746.
-[Cupcake grunting]
-[alarm blares]
[tense] 1746.
[alarm blares]
-[high pitched] 1747.
-[alarm blares]
[high pitched in song voice] 1747!
-[tense music playing]
[high pitched] 1748?
[welcoming beeps]
[high pitched] Yes! It was 1748.
Oh, thank God for that. Cupcake.
[whines]
[normal voice] Cupcake.
Cupcake, come on, you get out.
[door clicks]
[growls in determination] Right.
-Where are you?
-[curious music playing]
[sneakily] Are you over here?
[muted] Where are you?
[growls]
Huuh! Heh!
Come on…
-Come on.
-[music swells]
Oh my goodness. [gasps]
[whimpers and groans] Argh.
-[loud grunt]
-[thud]
[upbeat music playing]
-[grunts]
-[lid clunks]
[nervous humming]
[tearing]
-[exhales sharply]
-[drumroll and music fades]
[soft whimper]
-[sighs]
-[bustling music playing]
-[clink]
-[thuds]
[vaccum cleaner whirrs]
[loud sigh]
[bustling music stops]
[hopeful music plays]
[sighs cheerily] Huh.
[soft thud]
[drawer closes]
-Tsk.
-[squeaking]
Ugh.
Hm.
-[switch flicks]
-[hopeful music plays]
[switch flicks]
-[sighs with relief]
-[door opens]
-[switch flicks]
-[washing machine rumbles]
[water gurgling]
[zipping]
[happy music swells]
-[high pitched spinning]
-[rattling]
Hm.
[female voice] Please leave your message
after the tone.
[soft beep]
Sweetheart, it's just me again. Uh…
I'm just calling, uh,
to say I love you and
I miss you very much.
-And, uh… Oh…
-[phone rings]
-Dad.
-Darling! How are you?
Remember what I told you about
voicemails. No one does that anymore.
Oh, right, of course,
no voicemails. Sorry, I keep forgetting.
But isn't it great, sweet pea.
We're actually going to go away together.
I know. We're going
away together tomorrow.
Oh. Didn't you get my voicemail?
Oh no, of course,
you don't do, um, voice…
Um, well, the thing is sweet pea,
I've managed to get a job.
Amazing.
Mum! Dad got a job!
-[mum] What?
-I told you he would.
Oh, but wait.
Can we still go away tomorrow?
Ah, no, well that's
the thing. It'll have to be next week.
Oh, uh, wait. Next week?
Oh, hello Jess.
Sorry, yes, I have to
work this week now, so…
So you just want me to
change all my plans for you, Trevor?
Well, yes, ideally.
Do you have any idea
how difficult that's going to be?
Are you doing that thing again
where you don't move your face
and pretend the line's frozen?
Uh, no. No. No, I was just… sorry Jess,
all this has happened so last minute.
-Please, Mum.
-Oh for God's sake.
How can you be even
more annoying after the divorce?
So what is this job, anyway?
Well, I'm house-sitting.
So the job is just sitting
around a house all day doing nothing?
You finally found
something you're good at.
Well, actually, it's harder
than it sounds. You see there's--
Let's just talk about this
tomorrow, Trevor. Bedtime.
Yeah. Dad, I've got to go.
-Let's just keep in touch…
-[mum] Maddy!
and I love you
to the moon and ba-- uh… you've gone.
[high pitched] 1513.
-[high-pitched] Night setting.
-[beeps]
-[sighs]
-[sniffs]
[mysterious music playing]
-Ohh!
-[music builds and stops]
[resounding alarm blares]
[Trevor screams desperately]
1746! Er, 17… 1747! 1748!
[closing theme music playing]